This is DuoSign. Right now, 430 million
people worldwide are deaf or hard of
hearing. And the technology we built in
the past has mostly gone in one direction,
helping people understand them. DuoSign
goes the other way. You type, you speak,
there are Avatar signs. No interpreter, no
app to download. Happens right here in
your browser. So here we are. This is the
main screen. We've got the dark mode,
light mode toggle. For this tutorial, I'll
do it in dark mode. Here's the
profile menu. So DuoSign allows you to have
three free transcriptions. But once you
sign in, you're able to have access for
all. So I'm going to type the text, "Hello
viewers". And you're going to see
that sign as well. This avatar is going to
perform the sign again. And as you can
see, it's a bit wonky. But this is just
version one. Over here is our history
page. So in the history page, you can see
all the translations that were done. You
can look at them, you can export them as
video, and you can hit download. In our
settings page, we have a load of settings
you can choose from to customize however
you like it. Over here, I'm going to enter
some text. I'm going to say "help me find
the duster". The avatar is
going to perform that sign. And the best
part is I can download this video. So you
can also change the avatar mode from full
body or close-up or a 3D world view, where
you can see the avatar in full 3D and
interact with it. If you get lost or want
to understand how DuoSign works, there's
some documentation to help you. You can
read all about it here. DuoSign isn't
perfect yet. The vocabulary is just 2,000
words. The avatar is still improving. But
it's free and it's going to be free just
for you. As such, it's very important that
when you're done using the app, you do
take part in the survey and tell us what
part of DuoSign you liked and what part
you didn't like and how we can improve it
further. You can tell us your thoughts.
You can leave bad reviews if you like.
Just be honest and be transparent. We'll
be working on it and we'll definitely be
sending you updates from time to time on
the progress of our app.